Guide to the Robert Sutherland Lord Papers, 1890-2013 UA.90.F101
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio Material, 1953-2006; IX.
  - Photo of W.H. Longhurst, CD (Box 20, Item 1)
  - Variations on Adeste, fideles, 1999; CD (Box 20, Item 2)
  - Robert Lord at Bethany Lutheran Church, 2002; CD (Box 20, Item 3)
  - Organ Performance, undated; CD (Box 20, Item 4)
  - Final Faculty Organ Concert, 1999; CD (Box 20, Item 5)
  - Mozart Variation; Happy Birthday, 2006; CD (Box 20, Item 6)
  - L'Organo, Organ Recital Series, Piccolo Spoleto, 2006; CD (Box 20, Item 7)
    Fantasia nad Fugue in G; Sei Fioretti; Medieval Suite; Fantasia on a Chorale,
  - Wedding Music & Interview, 1975-1977; Cassette (Box 21, Item 1)
  - Varied Perfomances, 1974; Cassette (Box 21, Item 2)
  - Lord on Bach No. 1, 1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 3)
  - Lord on Bach No. 3, 1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 4)
  - Lord on Bach No. 4, 1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 5)
  - Lord on Bach No. 5 and No. 6, 1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 6)
  - Lord on Bach No. 7 and No. 8, 1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 7)
  - Lord on Bach No. 14, 1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 8)
  - Lord on Bach No. 23 and No. 24, 1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 9)
  - Program No. 3, undated; Cassette (Box 21, Item 10)
  - Lord on Bach (unknown program), undated; Cassette (Box 21, Item 11)
  - Lord on Bach (No. 21), 1974-1978; Cassette (Box 21, Item 12)
  - Robert Sutherland Lord and Jim Cunningham, 1999; Cassette (Box 21, Item 13)
  - Sunday Arts Magazine; unknown; interview, 1978-1991; Cassette (Box 21, Item 14)
  - Interview with RSL, 1991; Cassette (Box 21, Item 15)
  - Pipe Dreams (dedication), undated; Cassette (Box 21, Item 16)
  - Pipe Dreams Heinz Chapel Choir, 2001; Cassette (Box 21, Item 17)
  - Bach Series, undated; Cassette (Box 21, Item 18)
  - Tournememire - Improvisation on "Ultimate Pasubali" at Paroisse Sainte Clotilde, 1953-1979; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 1)
  - Toccata and Fugue in D Minor, 1978 (Box 22, Item 2)
  - Lord I, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 3)
  - Prelude and Fugue in E Minor; When in deepest need; through adam's fall; in thee is Joy; Prelude in B Minor, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 4)
  - Rhapsody for Organ, D. Godfrey, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 5)
  - Lord Untitled 1, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 6)
  - Lord Untitled 2, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 7)
  - Lord Untitled 3, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 8)
  - 15 Recordings, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 9)
  - Lord Untitled 4, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 10)
  - 10th Anniversary of the Dedication of the Organ in the Rotunda of the Henry Clay Frick Fine Arts, 1974; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 11)
  - Tuesday Noon Concert, 1975; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 12)
  - Tournemire - 7 Parolis, 1977; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 13)
  - Fugue in G Major; Fantasia in G; Fugue G Minor & E minor; Toccata and Fugue in D minor, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 14)
  - Ein' feste Burg ist unser Gott; Fugue in B Minor on a theme of Corelli, 1977; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 15)
  - Pastorale in F Major Pt. 2-4, 1977; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 16)
  - Lord II, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 17)
  - Tuesday Noon Organ Concerts, Tape 1, 1977; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 18)
  - Tuesday Noon Organ Concerts, Tape 2, 1977; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 19)
  - Lord Untitled 5, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 20)
  - Celestrial Autumn, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 21)
  - Allein Gott in der Höh; Chorlae Partita on Sei gegrüsset, 1977; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 22)
  - Lord Untitled 6, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 23)
  - Tournemire (1 of 2), 1978; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 24)
  - Tournemire (2 of 2), 1978; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 25)
  - Robert Lord at St. Clotilde, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 26)
  - Lord Untitled 7, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 27)
  - Dedication Recital by Robert S. Lloyd at Edgewood Church, New Haven, CT, 1959; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 28)
  - Lord Untitled 9, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 29)
  - Lord Untitled 10, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 30)
  - Lord Untitled 11, undated; Open Reel (Box 22, Item 31)
  - Heinz Memorial Concert Series, Sunday September 24, 2006 3:00 PM, Digital File
  - Dr. Robert Sutherland Lord in Concert on the Reuter Organ, Heinz Memorial Chapel, University of Pittsburgh, October 26, 2003; Digital File
  - Dr. Robert Sutherland Lord Composer, Variations on Adeste Fideles, 1999; Digital File
  - L'Organo Organ Recital Series Piccolo Spoleto, June 2, 2006; Digital File
  - Heinz Memorial Concert Series, Sunday September 18, 2005 3:00 PM, Digital File
  - Robert Sutherland Lord at Bethany Lutheran, November 10, 2002; Digital File
  - London Symphonies, The University of Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, Roger Zahab, Music Director, Robert Sutherland Lord, Organ, ca. 1999-2006; Digital File
  - Heinz Memorial Concert Series, Sunday April 17, 2005 3:00 PM
  - Dr. Robert Sutherland Lord, Heinz Memorial Concert, September 24, 2000, 3:00 PM
  - Trinity Cathedral Spring Recital Series, 2004, Dr. Robert Sutherland Lord, Professor, Digital File
  - Dr. Robert Sutherland Lord, Concert Heinz Chapel, December 31, 1994; Digital File
  - Final Facutly Organ Concert, Dr. Robert Sutherland Lord, University Organist, Heinz Memorial Chapel, University of Pittsburgh, March 21, 1999; Digital File
  - Robert Lord 3 Music Tracks, ca. 1999-2006; Digital File
  - Robert Sutherland Lord, Mozart Variations, Happy Birthday, March 23, 2006; Digital File
  - Heinz Memorial Chapel Concert, Robert Sutherland Lord with Pitt Orchestra, March 16, 2006; Digital File
  - Heinz Chapel, Jean Langlais, Robert Lord; St. Paul Cathedral, Nickolas Danby and Odile Pierre; St. Paul's Episcopal, Hector Olivera; Holy Comforter, Hector Olivera, ca. 1972-1980; Digital File